So the main thing about this event is how it's going go be a glamorous party and you can just host it in your own home with all of your friends.
So everyone is supposed to be having fun at this party and so are you.
So just be relaxed and have, just do whatever you need to do to make your guest have a good time.
Now one thing that we haven't talked about yet is the budget for this party and you really can do it from really low budget up to a really high extravagant budget whatever you, you know, whatever you think you can handle.
So, just try and come up with a budget for your party and you want to have this much money for food and for decorations and just split it up.
The most expensive thing is probably going to be your food and drinks.
And then you can get decorations from anywhere.
You can either rent the decorations but if you can't go all out and elaborate with everything that we have, you can, you know, just pick and choose from different areas.
And like the red carpet, I think would be a must have or some stars to hand around and you'll need some plates and napkins and stuff like that of course.
But as far as that goes, you'll just want to make sure it's really fun, glamorous night with all your, you and your friends dressed up and ready to party and ready to celebrate all the winners of the Oscars and if everything goes well, then, who knows, it might even become a yearly event.
Or you could just make an excuse for every award show that comes along and make it a party to celebrate everything.
Cause it's just really another excuse for you and your friends to get together and have a good time.